question_data = [
		{
			"category": "History",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "The Spitfire originated from a racing plane.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": ["False"]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.",
			"correct_answer": "False",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"True"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "Faust is a playable character in &quot;Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator&quot;.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "Luigi is taller than Mario?",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "History",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "The United States was a member of the League of Nations.",
			"correct_answer": "False",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"True"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Politics",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "The 2016 United States Presidential Election is the first time Hillary Clinton has run for President.",
			"correct_answer": "False",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"True"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "General Knowledge",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.",
			"correct_answer": "False",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"True"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "There is a Donald Trump Board Game, which was made in 1989.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
			]
		},
		{
			"category": "Entertainment: Television",
			"type": "boolean",
			"difficulty": "easy",
			"question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klaang is a typical Klingon male.",
			"correct_answer": "True",
			"incorrect_answers": [
				"False"
			]
		}
	]